

Career Objectives

I'm a multi-disciplinary web designer and developer with over 5 years of professional experience. I make companies of any size stand out and reach their audience through clean, intelligent design and hand-crafted, innovative web experiences that look great regardless of browser or device.

Professional Experience

RevZilla (2013+)

Front End Developer (2018+)

- Maintain an e-commerce Platform with over 15k daily visitors and 5.4MM in annual sales.
- Ensure the delivery of high code quality through reviews, demos, pair programming and utilizing services like GitHub and CircleCI.
- Consistently deliver work on-time and under-budget in an Agile work environment.

User Experience Designer (2016 - 2018)

- · Crafted the look and feel of the site with concise product requirements, user stories, and wireframes.
- · Guided key business decisions with over 250 A/B tests gathering crucial performance data.
- Guaranteed the usability of a website redesign by putting responsive, interactive prototypes in the hands of users before launch.

Visual Designer (2013 - 2016)

- Generated over 1MM+ in revenue with on-site promotional graphics and email marketing.
- Optimized website usability with beard-scale difficulty illustrations, size chart graphics and clean UI.
- Led design team exploration and discovery by hosting monthly meetings and regularly sharing "Frank's Tips" featuring new processes, tools and tips with the department.

Philadelphia Rock Gyms (2017+)

Freelance Web Developer

- $\bullet\,$ Modernized the PRG Brand with their first complete website relaunch in 5+ years.
- Enhanced the user experience by reorganizing the information architecture and speeding up the website performance.
- · Satisfied the client by maintaining clear expectations and keeping consistent communication.

M. Night Shyamalan Foundation (2017+)

Freelance Web Developer

- Contributed to over 100k in donations for the organization by preparing the website for their annual Shyamaween event
- Increased site performance 30% by conducting a website audit and facilitating a web domain and hosting transfer.

Jewelry Appraisals, Inc. (2016+)

Freelance Web Designer & Developer

- Refreshed the JA Inc. brand with a clean, beautiful new logo, color palette, photography and redesigned digital experience.
- · Streamlined the appraisal process with a completely custom and unique desktop application.

Personal Information

Website: frankluongo.com

Email: frank@frankluongo.com

Phone: (570) 972-6641

Github: github.com/frankluongo92

About Me

I am passionate about making things better; better for the user, for the business and for the world. I love problem solving, researching and testing every solution until we find what's right. Whether it's through visual design, UX, development or a combination of disciplines, my ultimate goal is always to build something meaningful.

Education

Drexel University, Philadelphia BS in Graphic Design 2011 - 2015

Skills

Development

- HTML
- · CSS, SCSS
- JavaScript, Electron, ES6, jQuery, React.js
- Bootstrap, Foundation
- Elixir, PHP, Ruby on Rails
- MySQL
- WordPress, Shopify

User Experience

- Creating User Personas
- Writing Product Requirements
- · Performing User Studies and Site Audits
- Designing Workflows and Wireframes
- · Building Prototypes

Visual Design

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe llustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Sketch
- Framer